

## **CONTACT**

+506-72848535



Liberia, Guanacaste, Costa Rica



rodrigovidal278@gmail.com



rodrigo-vidal-portafolio.netlify.app



github.com/vidal1101

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA**



@rodrigovidalc



@rodrigovidalc



@Rodrigo\_Vidal\_C

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript

Java

Python

Dart

Flutter

Bootstrap

SqlServer

Docker

Git-Github

PHP

# **RODRIGO VIDAL CANALES**

#### Software Developer

Developer of mobile and web applications with knowledge in back-end and front-end, developed through own projects and with experience at the business level. I seek to develop my career, helping to contribute with my skills and learn from others through good communication to achieve final designs that meet the needs and preferences of clients.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **App Codimed - Flutter Freelance**

June 2022 a september 2022 mobile application with flutter SDK for medical control services

#### Web developer - Internship at Rolosa company

November 2021 - May 2022 (6 months) development of custom modules using drupal cms

#### **Web programmer - Freelance**

March 2019 a September 2019

Creation of a web system of point of sale and accounting, developed in python

## **EDUCATION**

## Diplomado en Ingeniería en Tecnologías de Información

Diploma in technology with knowledge in hadware and equipment software.

## **COURSES**

#### **UDEMY- FLUTTER**

Development of mobile applications for ios and android.

## REFERENCES

Andrey Quesada Méndez +506-87024823 aquesada@rolosa.com